Lesson 17.
Carol tells Bob the good news.
Carol phones Bob to tell him the cookies are selling very well,
and that she needs another 1000 by the morning.
Bob isn't sure he can make the cookies so quickly,
but Carol insists.
Bob, your wife's cookies are selling like hotcakes.
How many did you sell, Carol?
We've sold out.
I need more right away.
Bring me another 1000 by tomorrow at 9 a.m.
That's a tall order, Carol.
Don't blow it, Bob.
Susan scrumptious cookies could really take off.
I know, but I'm not sure we have enough time to bake all those cookies.
Bake all night if you have to.
Burn the midnight oil.
If you work hard now, you'll be sitting pretty in a few years.
Rest assured that I'll do my best to deliver the goods.
Okay, now let's stop the chitchat.
You've got work to do.